[tense music]
♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
- Allie. please. I'm not
saying you're a bad person.
- Oh. but I'm a racist?
How can you say that?
- Because you're white.
- So you're a racist too?
- Of course.
So is every otherwell-intentioned
"woke" millennial in Brooklyn.
- Okay. I know I'm new and all.
Spencer. but I--
- No. it's not an accusationor an insult.
It's just a fact.
- Okay. so. let's pretend
for the moment
anyway that I agree
with your premise.
Hey. Vicky.
- Hey.
- That all white people
are racist.
Now what?
What's the next step?
What do we. the decent. kind.
unintentional racists.
actually do about it?
- We should discussthis more in depth tonight.
Over dinner.
- Are you asking me on a date?
- Yeah. if that's okay.
I don't want to make you
feel uncomfortable.
- No. dinner sounds fun.
Still think your theory
is ridiculous.
- [chuckles]
Okay.
- Oh. my God.
[dramatic music]
What the hell's--
oh. my God!
- Run!
[overlapping screams]
- [whimpering]
[tense music]
- Well. we're glad
you're here. Tiffany.
- I'm glad to be here.
White Collar was fun and all.
but I didn't join the FBIto arrest accountants.
- [chuckling]
Right.
- By the way. what kind of nameis "Jubal"?
- "Jubal." it is--
well. it's. I guess a tribute
to my grandfather. theHonorable Jubal N. Valentine.
- Oh. it's like that.
- [chuckles]
Yeah. I guess.
Ah. so here. Stuart Scola.
This is your new partner.Tiffany Wallace.
- Oh.Nice to meet you.
I thought you were startingnext week.
- I got settled in a little
earlier than I thought.
- Great. well. looking forward
to working with you.
- Yeah. Tiffany spenttwo years in Atlanta
working white-collar. but she
grew up here in Brooklyn.
- Bed Stuy.
Thrilled to be back.
- Oh. Tiffany. this is--
- Hey. I'm Omar.
These guys call me "OA."
- Okay. listen up.
I just got a call.
There's been a mass shooting
in Greenpoint.
I want all hands on deck.
- Just like that.
[soft dramatic music]
♪
- Maggie Bell.
- [chuckles]
Hey.
- You're back?
- Yeah. I am.
We bump elbows or something?What are we doing?
- No. I think we can hug.
- Right.
- [chuckling]
[soft music]
Come on!
- So how did the undercover
gig go?
- Fine.
- Did you close the case?
- I made 16 arrests.
- Sounds like a home run.
- Look. I'm just happy
to be back here with you.
Playing "Maggie Bell" again.
I mean. it's not as glamorous
pretending to be somebody 24/7.
- But everything went well?
- Got the job done.
- What does that mean?
- It means that I'm ready
to move forward
and start a new chapter.
- Still need to be in control.
Copy that.
- So. how'd you like
"Hotlanta"?
- It was okay.
A little too Southern for me.but I had fun.
And just so you know. nobodycalls it "Hotlanta" anymore.
- Oh.
Got it.
It's the first time
I ever said it. too.
So why'd you leave NYPD?
- Man. I feel like I'm
on a bad first date!
- Oh.
Okay. I'm sorry.
Didn't mean to...
I thought "Hotlanta" would be
the most awkward moment
of the morning.
- Sorry. I'm just...
sometimes I'm justa little bit too blunt.
I left the NYPD
because I needed a change.
I got tired of talkingabout the Yankees.
the blue wall and hanging outat dive bars
called O'Sullivan'sand Murphy's.
- For the record.
I'm half Irish.
- Get a uniform to escort you.
- Right over here.
[indistinct chatter]
- Maggie Bell.
- Tiffany Wallace.
- Good to meet you.
- So what do we know?
- We've got four dead.
all in their 20s.
We've got two men. both white.
Two women.
One white. one Asian.
- Any witnesses?
- A few. but theydidn't see much.
The shooters
were wearing masks.
- We recover the casings?
- Yeah. we know the shooters
were using Krinkovs.
- Have you found
the shooters yet?
- Excuse me. sir.
can you back up?
- This is my company.
Those four people in body bagsare my employees.
I have a right to knowwhat's going on.
- You're absolutely right.
Let's take a walk.
We'll find a quiet place
we can talk.
♪
- All right. come on in!
Just talked to Maggie.
Here's what we know so far.
We got two shooters.
both firing Krinkovs.
Four victims. all journalists
at Echt Media.
- Known for its progressive
political commentary
and disruptive social ideas.
- Right.
They're liberal--most likely
extremely liberal. which means
we need to start digging
into right-wing hate groups.
Pull security cam footage
within a two-block radius.
Get to work. let's talk
to each other. people!
- Hey.
So Maggie and OAare on the scene.
Scola and Tiffanyare canvassing for witnesses.
but so far no actionable leads.
But dock is hot. so...
- Great. thanks.
- Yeah.
Oh. hey. uh...
Got a text from Kristen.She's moving to Dallas. huh?
- Yeah.
Yeah. she wanted
a change of scenery.
It's her decision.
- Right.
Okay. well... as long
as she's happy. I guess.
- She is.
- I wasn't awareof any specific threats.
but we do get hundreds ofnon-specific threats every day.
- Well. what do you mean
by that?
- Well. there's so much hatein the air.
No matter what you say.the other side is constantly
on the attack.
and it's personal.
You know. it used to be all
this political and social
vitriol was just rhetoric.
Now it's like we are actually
on the verge of a civil war.
- Well. have you posted
anything controversial
the past few days?
Anything that would agitate
a certain political
or ethnic group?
- It's our goal to publish
something controversial
every day.
It's our business model.
I'm happy to answerany other questions you have.
but I should go.
I need to talk
to the employees.
- Okay. sir. that's not how--
- Hey.
Just got a textfrom my informant.
He may have a lead.
- You guys out here
when the shooting went down?
[whistles]
Excuse me.
I asked you a question.
- Yeah. I ain't answering.
- Did you hear
any gunshots. sir?
- Man. you deaf?
I just said I ain't talking!
- You ain't talking. why?
'Cause you're a tough guy?
- 'Cause you're the police.
- No. we're the FBI.
So let me ask you again.
Were you out here
when the shooting went down?
Yes or no?
- No.
- Aw. look at you.
Trying to be all hard
and make a statement.
- You don't know a damn
thing about me. lady.
- One. don't call me "lady."
Two. I know a lot about you.
Like that tattoo on your arm?
"BMW"?
Means you roll
with Brooklyn's Most Wanted.
which means you're connected
to the Trey-Nine Crips.
which means you probably
grew up in Brownsville.
I'm guessing the Tilden Street
Housing Projects.
♪
Another thing you should know.
Jalen.
is that lying to me ain't like
lying to some fat dude
in a blue uniform.
It's a felony.
You do time behind that crap.
So the second
I walk away from here.
I'ma pull every piece
of surveillance footage
I can find.
And if I see your sorry butt
out here at 8:27 a.m..
I'ma charge you with perjury.
- Wait. wait. wait. wait.
Wait.
Look. I was here.
I--I heard the gunshots.
- Then what?
- I saw two dudes wearing masks
jump into a blue car.
- What kind of car?
- I'm not sure.
A sedan?
Kia. maybe?
- It was nice doing business
with you. Jalen.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Nice work back there.
But you didn't need
to jump in like that.
I had everything under control.
- Oh. my bad.
I just reacted.
I knew who that dude was. what
buttons to press. so I did it.
But I'm sorry
if I offended you.
- No big deal.
Just thought I'd. you know...say something.
- I'm glad you did.
But for the record. Scola...
if you got a problem
with people speaking up.
if you got a lot of rules
about when and how
I'm supposed to talk to people.
you should let me know.
Now.
'Cause I don't roll like that.
- Well. neither do I.
So you got nothing
to worry about.
And I'd preferif you call me "Stuart."
- I'll let Jubal know
about the blue Kia.
- Hey.
- I'm sorry to bother you. man.
But I'm just--
I'm sorta freaking.
I was working last nightat that biker bar.
I was talking to these twodudes I know.
I've been working real hardthe past few weeks!
Anyway. they start talkingabout doing some crazy stuff.
Okay?Um...
"Making noise."They kept saying that.
"We're gonna makesome noise. bro."
I tried to find out what theywere talking about. but--
- You know these guys' names?
- Tyler and Eddie.
I don't know their last names.Didn't ask.
You told me. "Never askfor last names.
They'll think you're a cop."
[coughing]
I think it's possible thoseguys might have been involved
in that shooting this morning.
- What do you mean. "involved"?
- The guy who drove the car...
he was at the bar this morning.
- What the hell
are you talking about?
- He came by the bar
an hour ago.
He was real nervous.
He said he was driving a stolen
car with these two idiots.
Tyler and Eddie.
and then they jumped out
and started shooting.
- Who's this guy?
- He goes by Big Mike.
That's all I know.
- Big Mike. okay.
So I'm a little confused.
Bike Mike. he just came in
and volunteered
this info to you?
- I'm just telling youwhat happened. Omar.
But Big Mike's a good dude;
he didn't know they were
gonna start shooting.
- He didn't know?
Those guys
were carrying Krinkovs.
- He was scared.
- I would be. too.
but it doesn't matter
that he was scared.
He was involved.
So you need to go
find this guy now.
- Okay. I'll try. but--
he said he was going to Floridaor maybe Georgia?
♪
[screams]
Ugh!
- If you're really this upset.
why don't you go track down Big
Mike and get me a last name?
♪
- You got it. Omar.
- Okay.
♪
By the way.
talked to my buddy in D.C.
He might be able
to find you a job.
A real one.
- Appreciate you
looking out.
♪
- Okay. Zayne.
- Where are we on the names?
Tyler? Eddie? Big Mike?
Ring any bells with you guys?Narcotics. prison gangs?
- Still running screens.
but there are lots
of Eddies and Tylers out there.
Only a few "Big Mikes."
but nine match
the physical description.
- All right.What about the shooters' car.
the blue Kia?We have any video yet?
- Just pulled some footage
from a camera two blocks away.
- Okay. throw it up.
♪
Hey.
- Yeah. running the plate now.
♪
Okay. car is registered
to Nancy Moore. 53.
Address is 234 87th Street
in Williamsburg.
Car was reported stolen
at 7:47 this morning.
- There you go.
Reach out to Nancy.
find out where the car
was stolen.
pull any security footage
in the area.
you know the drill.
- Yeah. on it.
- All right. roll it.
[tense music]
- The crime scene is two
blocks east of this.
- Yeah. can you push in
on the driver's face?
♪
- The driver
is your informant?
- Yes. I just met with him.
He thought he might know
who was involved.
- But he never mentioned
that he was at the scene.
Or the fact that he
was driving the getaway car.
- [sighs]
Correct.
- All right.so what was he doing?
He was playing.
Fishing for information. right?
- No. maybe fishing
for absolution?
- How do you mean?
- He was nervous.
talking in circles.
He made up a story
about a guy named "Big Mike"
that was stealing a car
and driving around
with two other guys.
He didn't know
they were gonna start shooting.
He was probably just trying to
get close to the two shooters.
prove that he wasn't a cop.
- It doesn't matter.
Just get him in here.
Now.
- All right.
- Zayne. it's me. Omar.
Again. listen. man.
You gotta give me a call back.
I just got a call
from my buddy in D.C.
He said that there may be
an opening here in New York
for a surveillance specialist.
He wants to know if he
can meet with you today.
so just get back to me.
let me know.
All right.
His phone's off.
The calls keep going
straight to voicemail.
- Well. of course his
phone's off; he's on the run.
- Yeah. maybe.
But he's not a killer. Maggie.
I know what it looks like.
but he's a decent human being.
I mean. I met himat an anti-Muslim rally.
but he was just theremarching with a bunch of Arabs.
He wants to help.
He doesn't even care about.
getting paid. like. for real.
There is no way that he
would willingly participate
in a mass shooting.
- Okay.
- Maggie.
- Hey.
I thought you were
taking the week off.
- I thought you were too.
- This is Omar Zidan.
This is Nestor. who I workedthe undercover case with.
- Oh.
Nice to meet you.
Congratulations. I heard you
guys had some good results.
- We did well.
I had a lot of fun. too.
- I don't know if "fun"is the word I would use.
- She tends
to overthink things.
- Do I?
- Good to meet you. Omar.
Talk soon.
[elevator dings]
- Is he a good guy?
- He's a good agent.
Lead hostage negotiator.Runs Gang Unit.
- I asked if he was a good guy.
- He's all right.
A little too cocky for me.
- Zayne. it's me. Omar.
Open up!
Zayne!
Anybody home?
- Okay. we needto get a warrant.
- No. we don't
because there is
a spare key.
Right here. see?
Told you he was a good kid.
He trusts me.
Zayne. you home?
[suspenseful music]
- Clear.
♪
- OA?
- Oh. my God.
♪
- Either Zayne's a really
diligent informant.
or he's involved.
[telephone dialing]
Hey. Jubal?
I just sent you some photos.
Can you put them through
facial rec right away?
- I got two names:
Tyler Haddock and Eddie White.
- Somebody tell me about 'em.
- Haddock has three priors
originating from Plainfield.
New Jersey.
And the other guy. White.
has five priors
born and raised
in Staten Island.
- Gang affiliations?
- Looks like they're affiliated
with a group called
"Freedom Fighters."
- Okay. let's get
an address for these two.
Kelly. can you run
the surveillance video
from the warehouse back again?
Let's confirm
that Tyler and Haddock
are the two guys
leaving the scene.
- Okay. Haddock is 6'2".
White is 5'9".
Ford Fusion is...
- Is 57.7 inches.
That's four feet 10 inches?
- Okay. so. using the car
as a reference point.
that means the scale
is 11.9 inches.
Which means. Man 1.
White. is about 5'9".
And Man 2.
Haddock. is about 6'1".
- All right. that's close
enough. but we need more.
Can we zoom in?
See if we can find something.
[sighs]
What do we got?
What is that?
I think we got a tattoo.
Yeah. let's see
if he's got this tattoo.
"488."
Does that mean anything?
- No. but "1488" does.
Maybe there's a "1" under
the sleeve we can't see?
- Okay. let's assume there is.
What's it mean?
- The "14" stands for a 14-word
white supremacy slogan.
"We must secure
the existence of our people
and a future
for white children."
The "88" is code
for "Heil Hitler."
Eight equals "H." eighth letter
of the alphabet. so...
- Yeah. it's a match.
"1488."
It's among the listed tattoos
documented in Haddock's
last arrest.
- Get SWAT over there
right away.
I'll call Maggie and OA.
Good work.
[men whispering]
[suspenseful music]
- On you. Ready?
[grunts] FBI!
- High-tech. 12:00!
- [shouts]
- Come on. Scotty!
- Let's go!
- Zayne's going out the back!
- [indistinct]
We got two on the run!
- Zayne!
- Don't move!
♪
- FBI!
Stop. stop!
Stop!
♪
- OA. over there.
- Go. go. go!
I got him!
Scola. he's gone.
♪
- Zayne!
Zayne. ugh!
Zayne!
What are you doing?
♪
Who the hell are you?
- Connor Lang.
♪
- I told you. I had nothing
to do with that shooting.
- So why were youwith the two idiots who did?
- I stopped over
to have a beer.
- Why. to celebrate?
- It says here
that you're an associate
of the "Freedom Fighters."
is that true?
- Yeah. but that don't mean
I shoot people.
I was at home in bed
when that shooting happened.
I didn't leave my apartment
till noon.
I drove over to Gino's Pizza.
Go check for yourself.
There's a lot of cameras
in my building.
- Okay. we will.So...
You want us to believethat you just so happened
to go over to those guys' house
the same day they killedfour innocent people?
- You really want to know?
- Yeah. I do.
- I stopped over to see if
Eddie could fix my oil pump.
He's real good with engines.
- I feel like you
can do better than that. man.
- It's the truth!
- Look. I had no idea they went
over to Echt's
and started shooting people.
None.
Did what they had to do.
I guess.
- Sir. what did you just say?
"They did what they had to do"?
They killed fourinnocent people.
- If you work at Echt Media.
you ain't innocent.
They're the cause
for all this nonsense.
All they do is celebrate
the gays and the Blacks.
Talking about
how great they are
and how evil and stupid we are.
- You know who this guy is?
- Yeah. it's Zayne.
- He in your little club too?
"Freedom Fighters"?
- Yeah. I don't know.
I never asked.
But that dude's crazy.
Works over at this biker bar.
He's always talking trash
about Blacks. Puerto Ricans...
Arabs.
- Is that it?
- Mm.
So. what. can I go now?
[scoffs]
- OA?
- He still won't return
my calls or my texts.
- He's not going to respond.
Why are you asking
so surprised?
- Because I've known this kid
for two years.
He's a great informant.
And yeah. he's a little crazy
and he takes risks
but he gets results
and until this morning.
he has never lied to me.
Ever.
So forgive me
for being surprised
that he keeps blowing me off.
- Look. OA. I knowthat this has been hard. but...
obviously Zaynehas been hanging out
with these white supremacists.listening to their gripes.
their speeches.
- Yeah. so?
- Yeah. well.maybe their way of thinking
is starting to rub off.
Look. it is not easy lyingall day every day
pretending to be somebodythat you're not.
- I don't know who you think
you're talking to. Maggie.
I've been undercover.
Zayne did not flip.
No way.
- Okay. let me try thisanother way then.
I think you needto sit this one out.
- What the hell
are you talking about?
- You're too investedin Zayne's innocence.
It's blocking your judgement.
- Mm. no.
I'm good.
- Hey.
Did you guys getany useful information
about this Connor guy?
- Yeah.
We know he's a lunatic racist
who needs a new oil pump.
That's about it.
- And your informant?
Did you locate him?
- No.
- Wrong answer.
I just talked to DHS.
There's a lot of chatter
about a second attack
and it is coming
from the Freedom Fighters.
We need to find
your informant fast.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Mr. Wells. we're looking
for your son. Zayne.
It's important.
- What's going on?
Did he do something wrong?
- We think he may have
inadvertently gotten himself
mixed up with some
dangerous people.
- Well. Zayne was here
about an hour ago.
He was all over the place.
Pacing. talkinga mile a minute.
He wanted money.
Said he needed to move.buy a new phone.
- A new phone?
Has he called you
from that phone yet?
Yeah. like five minutes ago.
- Okay. could you give him
a call back?
Actually. could you
video chat him?
I just need you to say hello.
[phone ringing]
- Zayne?
- Hey. Dad.
- Hey. Zayne.
- Omar?
- What is going on?
- Hey. man.
- We know that you
were driving the car.
- I had no idea
those two dudes
were gonna
start shooting. man.
I swear to God!
- Okay. I believe you.
but you need to tell me
what is happening.
- I stole the car to try to
get in tight with those guys.
You know. I was trying
to sell my cover.
They were getting suspicious!
So I did what you told me
to do. you know?
Prove them wrong.
Act like a criminal. so I did.
And then...
and then they had me drive
to that warehouse in Brooklyn.
- Okay. I get it.
You were just doing your job.
But. look. stuff like this
is gonna happen.
- Are you gonna arrest me?
- Zayne. I didn't say that.
- A few hours ago. you said
the driver was involved.
And that he might as well
have pulled the trigger!
- Zayne. I am going
to help you.
but we need to meet up now.
- Meet me at the corner of.
uh... of Noble and West.
I'll be there in. like.
10 minutes. okay?
- Okay.
Thank you so much.
- Look!
I don't know what the hell
he got himself into.
but he's a good kid.
He was so excited when he knew
you were trying to get him
a legitimate job.
Please?
Don't hurt my son.
[somber music]
♪
- Oh. I got him.
He's two blocks east of here
heading east on Milton.
Zayne!
[dramatic music]
♪
[car horn beeping]
- [screams]
♪
- FBI. do not move!
- Why are you running. Zayne?
Huh?
- Hey. hey. let her go!
- Hey!
- Nobody come inside.
- Don't do this. Zayne!
Do not do this!
- I'll shoot everyone in here!
I swear to God!
♪
- What do we got?
- Seven hostages in total.
All appear to be adults.
Four women. three men.
- Is Vertiz on site yet?
- Yeah. he just landed.
I'll call Maggie and OA.
tell them he's in charge.
- Set up across the street.
Give me a clear shot. Kyle.
Now. go!
Open a line of communication.
See if we can hijack
the video feed.
- Agent Vertiz.I know the hostage taker.
He's my informant.
- Okay.
Anything I need to know?
- Despite what just happened.
yeah.
He's just scared. okay?
He got caught upin the shooting
this morning by accident.
- Okay. but that
doesn't really matter.
Not now--he's taken seven
innocent people hostage.
- I am aware of what it lookslike. but--
- I'll take it from here.
- Okay. but let me help.
- I said I'll take it
from here.
Good. good.
You're good--okay.
Open an angle
[indistinct].
We'll start on the left side.
and we'll move to the right.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Find anything interesting?
- Not yet.
Tyler and Eddiehad lots of devices.
so we still havelots of scrolling to do.
- Hey. I got something.
- Tell me.
- Incoming textto Tyler Haddock.
"Nice work on Echt.More fun coming soon."
- Run the phone.
- Can't locate it.
Must be a burner.
- OA.
The chatter is real.
A second attack is imminent.
- Please confirm.
do you have eyes on the target?
- Yes. sir. I have a clear shot
through the window
on the southwest corner.
- Okay. on my command.
- Don't shoot!
Don't shoot!
- What the hell are you doing?
We have intel
on a second attack.
- So?
- So Zayne is our best lead.
He might be able to help.
- Sir. I still have
a clean shot.
Please confirm. green light.
- Nestor. just let me
talk to him.
See what he knows. please.
- Sir. do I have the green?
- Stand down.Repeat. stand down.
- Thank you.
[phone ringing]
- Zayne?
It's me. Omar.
Listen. I am gonna help you
and everything is gonna be okay
but you need to let
those people go now.
- You think I'm stupid?
Four people are dead.
- Okay. listen to me. Zayne.
Let me rephrase myself.
I am only here to help you.
but the longer
you stay in there.
the worse this is gonna get.
so you need to come
to your senses now.
- I gotta get
out of the country.
Go someplace safe where
there's no extradition.
- Okay. okay.
We can do that.
We can look into someplace
with no extradition.
but you are gonna need to give
us something in exchange.
- Like what?
- Like the hostages.
- I already said no to that!
- Fine.
Then tell us what you know
about the second attack.
- Second attack?
Man.
How many times
do I have to tell you?
I didn't know anything
about the first attack!
- Did Tyler and Eddie
mention any other names?
Did they mention anything
about a second attack?
Did you meet any other
Freedom Fighters?
- I met a guy named William
at the bar. like...
three or four days ago.
- Okay. that's good.
Did you get a last name?
What's he look like?
- About--he's. like. mid-30s?
Had a beard.
The number 13 was tattooed
on his arm.
Tyler and Eddie. they were
in awe of this guy. okay?
They said he was...
a "true believer."
- Okay. okay. amazing.
You're helping us.
Now we can help you.
- All right. listen up--I need
the full name and address
of a man named William.
Male. white.
approximately 30 years old.
Has the number 13 tattooed
on his arm.
so he's either
a huge James Harden fan
or a member
of the Aryan Circle.
My money's on the latter.
so let's find this guy.
shall we?
- I have seven Williams
with ties
to white nationalist groups.
Four are under the age of 40
and only one lives in New York.
William Ellis. long rap sheet.
- William Ellis. check him out.
- Yep. looks like
he's a suspect
in a recent arson case as well.
- That's enough for now.
Find me the last known address.
- [grunts]
Federal agents.
- Clear immediate.
[ominous music]
♪
- Front's clear!
- Clear.
- Check the basement!
♪
[agent shouts indistinctly]
- Jubal. it's me.
Looks like Ellis is on the move
with a bomb.
- That's Ellis's car.
right there.
The black SUV. heading east on
123rd Street and Brooklyn.
- All right. all right.
Put out a BOLO right away
and let's get up on his phone
and into that vehicle's
LoJack system.
We need to find out
where he's going
and get there before he does.
Let's go. let's go!
- Hey!
You did really good. Zayne.
Okay. remembering the name
William was huge.
Everyone at the FBI
is very grateful.
But more importantly. they
believe you now. all right?
They know that you were just
trying to be a good informant.
But you're gonna need
to keep helping us.
so I need you
to let those hostages go
before anyone gets hurt.
And if you do that.
I can get you a good deal.
- Don't play me. Omar!
I want a--a car.
No. an SUV!
And I want a jet.
- No. no.
That is a bad idea. Zayne.
Okay? Enough.
- I don't care!
Do it. or I'll shoot
everyone in here.
I swear to God!
- Zayne. Zayne. don't--
[suspenseful music]
- Jubal?
We're tracking Ellis's SUV.
- All right. eyes up.
- He's crossed the Triborough.
- Where's he going?
Where's he going?
- Heading west.
To Washington Heights!
We just got up on his phone.
His internet. there are
lots of searches
relating to Trans For Life.
a nonprofit.
Address is... 14 165th Street.
- That's the target.
Throw it up!
Get a team of agents
over there right away
and pull up any
and all live video feeds
in and around the target.
Scola. head over
to 14 165th Street now.
Ellis is gonna attack
Trans For Life.
- Trans For Life office
is over there.
SWAT's clearing the building
as we speak.
- Are we sure Ellis is actuallyhere in the vicinity?
- According to Jubal.
the last visual contact
was at 163rd and Riverside.
- Probably found
a place to park.
which means he's on foot
walking north
towards the office building.
I'll go east. you go west.
[suspenseful music]
♪
- I got eyes
on Ellis's vehicle.
It's parked on the south side
of 162nd.
Exact address is 122 162nd.
♪
Car's empty. and I want a bomb
team out here right away.
This thing could be rigged.
[phone ringing]
- Hey. what's going on?
- Any sign of William?
- No. I haven't seen him.
But what's up with that SUV?
- It's clean. but the dogs
detected chemicals.
so it's likely a bomb
was in the vehicle
within the past hour or so.
meaning...
- Ellis is carrying it.
- We also found a pamphlet
for another charity.
It's "Black and Proud NYC"
on Broadway.
Could be we're chasing
the wrong target.
- Okay. I'm heading west now.
- Okay. good.
I'm sending the SWAT team
there now to evacuate.
- Hold up.
I see him.
He's wearing blue jeans.
a tan jacket.
and he's carrying
a blue backpack.
- Okay. wait for backup.
- He's headed towards
the building. the target.
- Okay. okay.
I'm sending a team to you now.
♪
- William Ellis!
FBI.
Stop walking.
I said stop walking!
Are you sure there's a bomb
in that backpack?
'Cause this dude
is not complying.
- Yes. I told you.
the dog got a chemical hit.
- I've had dogs alert
to bubble gum. bruh.
What I'm asking is.
is the dog good?
Can I trust him?
- Yes.
- Are you sure?
- Trust me.
[disconnect tone]
- William Ellis!
Put your hands up
and stop walking!
I will not ask again!
♪
- [heavy breathing]
[tense music]
♪
- Backpack is hot.
Going to try and defuse it.
- I told you that dog was good.
- I know.
Thanks.
- Good news--
we just took Ellis down.
He was pronounced dead
at the scene.
He had a pipe bomb
in his backpack.
- Okay.
It means our friend Zayne
is no longer an asset.
Keep talking to him.
Make him comfortable.
And then lure him to the window
on the southwest side
of the café.
Tell him there's an SUVthere waiting for him.
- No. I can't do that.
- I'm not asking.
- He's my informant.
my friend.
- Yeah. but how he's taken
seven people hostage.
- I'll go inside.
If I talk to him in person.
I can get him to surrender.
- That's a really dumb idea.
- Yeah. well.
it's a hell of a lot better
than trying to take him out
with a sniper rifle
from 50 yards.
What if you miss. huh?
He'll snap and light up every
single person in that café.
- Stand down. Zidan.
Hey. you going in there
elevates the risk!
- Yeah. for me.
Not the hostages.
- You're too close
to this guy.
- No.
I can do this.
and I know what's at stake.
[somber music]
And. if necessary. I will take
him out in a heartbeat.
- Nestor?
♪
Give him a shot.Let him do his thing.
If OA says he can do it.he can do it.
You can trust me.
♪
- You have five minutes.
then I'm doing it my way.
Anyone dies. anyone gets hurt.
it's on you.
[suspenseful music]
♪
- Zayne.
I'm coming in!
- That's not a good idea.
- Yeah. I know.
A lot people seem to feel
that way. too.
But I'm gonna go ahead
and come in anyway. all right?
- No. Omar.
Don't!
- It's just me.
- Okay?
It's just me.
- So calm down.
We're gonna figure this out.
- Put your gun down.
- Okay. okay.
♪
Now you put yours down--
it's only fair.
- No.
It doesn't work that way.
- Okay. fine.
I know you're not
gonna hurt me.
And I know you're not gonna
hurt those people.
because you are a good kid.
Zayne.
- Quit playing me. Omar!
- Why do you keep saying that?
Zayne. I have never
lied to you ever.
- Really?
You lied to me earlier today.
- What are you talking about?
- You never texted your friend
at the FBI.
That was just a bunch of crap
to get me investedin the mission!
You're just using me!
Yeah.
Show me your phone.
Yeah. I want to see the text.
Come on.
Or. you know what?
You. big guy.
Get up.
Come right over here.
And get on your knees.
Omar. I swear to God.
show me your phone
or I'm gonna shoot this guy.
- Prepare to engage.
- Yes. sir.
He's on me.
♪
- Come on!
- Okay. okay.
You wanna do this your way?
♪
Okay.
It's there. take it.
You're gonna have to scroll.
The name is "Robert Harper."
♪
Keep going.
- I. uh...
♪
You really texted him?
- Yeah. man.
Come on.
- I'm sorry.
Uh...
I'm not--I'm not thinking
so good.
- I know.
So put the gun down
and let these people go.
and you and me
are gonna figure this out.
You have my word. Zayne.
Come on. Zayne.
Put it down.
Please. put it down.
♪
- [crying]
- Go. go.
Guys!
[somber music]
♪
- [crying]
- [sighs]
What the hell. Zayne?
♪
- [crying]
- Told you he'd get it done.
- Yeah. he did.
But you put mein a bad position.
- Oh. how's that?
- I didn't needanother opinion to process
at that particularmoment in time.
- I know. it was a very
stressful situation.
But you know that I'm only ever
trying to get the best result.
- I know.
I know. okay.I'll see you in a few?
- Yeah. right.
The medal ceremony.
- It's gonna be great.
come on.
- It's not funny!
- Don't beat yourself up.
Things happen.
Things out of our control.
It's part of the job.
- Yeah. I know that.
- Okay. so when
the ADIC calls your name.
walk up there
with a proud smile on your face
and grab that damn medal.
Okay?
'Cause you deserve it.
Without you. we never would
have made that case.
- Thank you.
[soft dramatic music]
♪
Okay.
See you later.
- Bye.
- Do you need any help
with the paperwork?
- [sighs]
No. I got it.
New guy does the paperwork.
Don't worry. I know the rules.
I punched my lieutenant
in the face.
That's the reason
I left the NYPD.
- Oh.
- He was drunk and he said
something pretty disgusting.
so I hit him.
I got him good. too.
A couple months later.
an ASAC I know
asked me
if I would be interested
in working with the FBI.
so I jumped.
♪
See you tomorrow.
- Well. look at you.
- Hey. [chuckles]
Uh. yeah.
I'm. uh. gussied up.
- I don't know what that means.
- It just means I'm dressed up.
I'm. um. getting
a gold medal tonight
for my extraordinary
and courageous efforts
in connection
with Operation Powder. so...
- Well. congratulations.That's amazing.
- Thanks. yeah.
- Before you go. though. um...
I wanted to thank you forstanding up for me with Nestor.
It really meant a lot.
- Of course.
I'm just really glad
that it worked out.
You know. I could see that
it was hard for you.
You clearly care about Zayne.
Probably tough to watch him
blow up his life like that.
- It is what it is.
- I don't want to be late.
- Go. go. I'll see you there!
- You're coming?
- Oh. yeah.
It's not every day that my
partner gets a gold medal.
- Okay.
- Okay. what's going on
with you?
- What?
- Why are you so unexcited?
The operation
was a huge success.
You arrested 16 people.
- Yeah. that's true.
We also killed someone.
Her name was Anna.Um...
She was married
to one of the targets.
She had just turned 22.
You know. I'd spent a lot
of time with her
and I considered her a friend.
The day of the arrest.
she panicked.
And she grabbed a knife
and she ran
towards one of the officers.
[melancholy music]
I shot her.
I didn't have a choice.
[sighs]
But we made 16 arrests. right?
So that's what matters.
I really should go.
I don't want to be late.
Like you said. not every day
you get a gold medal. right?
♪
[dramatic music]
[wolf howls]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm